var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is a) reward",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "658",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1425",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2836",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "553",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمِينِ",
        "answer": "[the] secure",
        "pcklId": "584",
        "tlit": "l-amīni",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانَ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-insāna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدُ",
        "answer": "after (this)",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "baʿdu",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَلَدِ",
        "answer": "[the] city",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-baladi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالتِّينِ",
        "answer": "By the fig",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-tīni",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنِ",
        "answer": "(the) best",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "aḥsani",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَحْكَمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Most Just",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bi-aḥkami",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاكِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Judges",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "l-ḥākimīna",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We created",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the judgment",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "bil-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَدَدْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We returned him",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "radadnāhu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالزَّيْتُونِ",
        "answer": "and the olive",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-zaytūni",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْفَلَ",
        "answer": "(to the) lowest",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "asfala",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَافِلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of the) low",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sāfilīna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطُورِ",
        "answer": "And (the) Mount",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waṭūri",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "never",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْوِيمٍ",
        "answer": "mould",
        "pcklId": "605",
        "tlit": "taqwīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُكَ",
        "answer": "causes you to deny",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "yukadhibuka",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is not",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَمْنُونٍ",
        "answer": "ending",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "mamnūnin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "95",
        "ayah": "6"
    }
]; 
export default words;